A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1981-1990 FA402
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1985; 0.41 Cubic Feet 31 microfilm reels (35mm); 31 Reels 31 microfilm reels (35mm)
  - Australia, 1985; 1985/410
    - C-V, 1985 (Reel 28, Frame 506)
  - Caribbean Region and Central America, 1985; 1985/420
    - K-U, 1985 (Reel 28, Frame 537)
  - Canada, 1985; 1985/427
    - A-Y, 1985 (Reel 28, Frame 544)
  - Ceylon, 1985; 1985/462
    Sri Lanka
    - Jaywardena, S.D.G., 1985 (Reel 28, Frame 812)
  - India, 1985; 1985/464
    - B-T, 1985 (Reel 28, Frame 831)
    - India - Fellowships, 1985; 1985/464.E
      - Padayatty, Joseph D., 1985 (Reel 28, Frame 926)
  - Malaysia, 1985; 1985/473
    - S-U, 1985 (Reel 28, Frame 934)
  - Africa, 1985; 1985/475
    - A-S, 1985 (Reel 28, Frame 954)
  - Kenya, 1985; 1985/476
    - A-N, 1985 (Reel 28, Frame 988)
  - Rhodesia, 1985; 1985/483
    - University of Zimbabwe (Petropoulos, E.A.), 1985 (Reel 29, Frame 1)
  - South Africa Region, 1985; 1985/487
    - Mananga Agricultural Management Centre, 1985 (Reel 29, Frame 13)
  - Cape of Good Hope, 1985; 1985/489
    - B-U, 1985 (Reel 29, Frame 28)
  - Uganda, 1985; 1985/492
    - Makerere University (B-K), 1985 (Reel 29, Frame 571)
  - West Africa, 1985; 1985/495
    - International Center for Bantu Civilizations, 1985 (Reel 29, Frame 577)
  - Nigeria, 1985; 1985/497
    - L-U, 1985 (Reel 29, Frame 791)
  - France, 1985; 1985/500
    - B-O, 1985 (Reel 29, Frame 869)
  - Senegal, 1985; 1985/531
    - Council for the Development of Economic and Social Research in Africa (Bujra, Abdulla S.), 1985 (Reel 30, Frame 1)
  - China, 1985; 1985/601
    - Arts Program Trip, 1985 (Reel 30, Frame 7)
    - A-Z, 1985 (Reel 30, Frame 99)
    - China - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1985; 1985/601.D
      - 601D, 1985 (Reel 30, Frame 342)
    - China - Fellowships, 1985; 1985/601.E
      - Li Haimin, 1985 (Reel 30, Frame 433)
  - Taiwan, 1985; 1985/605
    - Asian Vegetable Research Development Center, 1985 (Reel 30, Frame 436)
  - Japan, 1985; 1985/609
    - M-T, 1985 (Reel 30, Frame 440)
    - Japan - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1985; 1985/609.D
      - H-S, 1985 (Reel 30, Frame 534)
  - Korea, 1985; 1985/613
    - Min, Kyonghee, 1985 (Reel 30, Frame 544)
  - Thailand, 1985; 1985/617
    - A-U, 1985 (Reel 30, Frame 547)
  - Holland, 1985; 1985/650
    - University of Utrecht (Comparative Physiology), 1985 (Reel 30, Frame 645)
  - Austria, 1985; 1985/705
    - H-I, 1985 (Reel 30, Frame 659)
  - Belgium, 1985; 1985/707
    - Eychmans, Luc, 1985 (Reel 30, Frame 776)
  - Belgian Congo, 1985; 1985/709
    - C-M, 1985 (Reel 30, Frame 786)
  - Denmark, 1985; 1985/713
    - Nansen, Peter, 1985 (Reel 30, Frame 792)
  - Germany, 1985; 1985/717
    - I-V, 1985 (Reel 30, Frame 798)
  - Italy, 1985; 1985/751
    - Savioli, Lorenzo, 1985 (Reel 30, Frame 819)
  - Norway, 1985; 1985/767
    - Bjune, Gunnar, 1985 (Reel 30, Frame 826)
  - Mozambique, 1985/779
    Mozambique
    - Mozambique - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1985; 02.1985/779.D
      - 779D, 1985 (Reel 30, Frame 839)
  - Sweden, 1985; 1985/800
    - B, 1985 (Reel 30, Frame 843)
  - Switzerland, 1985; 1985/803
    - C-R, 1985 (Reel 30, Frame 857)
  - Egypt, 1985; 1985/812
    - A-L, 1985 (Reel 30, Frame 935)
  - Israel, 1985; 1985/825
    - B-T, 1985 (Reel 30, Frame 972)
  - Lebanon, 1985; 1985/833
    - Nasr, Julinda Abu, 1985 (Reel 31, Frame 1)
  - Members and Meetings, 1985; 1985/903
    - D-W, 1985 (Reel 31, Frame 32)
  - Humanities, 1985/911
    - Humanities - Fellowships, 1985; 1985/911.E
      - American Institute of Early History and Culture (Resident Fellows), 1985 (Reel 31, Frame 337)
      - B-G, 1985 (Reel 31, Frame 478)
      - K-S, 1985 (Reel 31, Frame 704)
  - Geographic Medicine, 1985/928
    - Geographic Medicine - Schistosomiasis, 1985; 1985/928.W
      Schistosomiasis
      - Hassan, Amr, 1985 (Reel 31, Frame 1316)
- General Correspondence, 1986; 0.45 Cubic Feet 34 microfilm reels (35mm); 34 Reels 34 microfilm reels (35mm)
  - International, 1986; 1986/100
    - Lyman, Richard W. (A-C), 1986 (Reel 1, Frame 1)
    - Warren, Kenneth S. (Diseases of Travelers and Immigrants), 1986 (Reel 1, Frame 446)
    - A-K, 1986 (Reel 1, Frame 903)
    - L-T, 1986 (Reel 2, Frame 1)
  - Requests for Information, 1986; 1986/102
    - Directories (A-W), 1986 (Reel 2, Frame 69)
  - International Organizations, 1986; 1986/103
    - United Nations (F-W), 1986 (Reel 2, Frame 86)
    - A-I, 1986 (Reel 2, Frame 285)
    - M-T, 1986 (Reel 2, Frame 818)
    - U-W, 1986 (Reel 3, Frame 1)
  - IPP (International Potato Program), 1986; 1986/107
    - International Potato Center (Genetic Engineering), 1986 (Reel 3, Frame 354)
  - CIAT (International Center for Tropical Agriculture), 1986; 1986/110
    - C-S, 1986 (Reel 3, Frame 456)
  - ILCA (International Livestock Center for Africa), 1986; 1986/113
    - International Livestock Centre for Africa, 1986 (Reel 3, Frame 484)
  - ICRISAT (International Crops Research Institute for the Semi-Arid Tropics), 1986; 1986/116
    - International Crops Research Institute for the Semi-Arid Tropics, 1986 (Reel 3, Frame 585)
  - ICIPE (International Center of Insect Physiology and Ecology), 1986; 1986/117
    - Regional Pest Management Research, 1986 (Reel 3, Frame 648)
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 1986; 1986/120
    - K-T, 1986 (Reel 3, Frame 700)
  - Greater Voice for Africa in the United States (Africa Policy Watch Project), 1986; 1986/121
    - A-M, 1986 (Reel 4, Frame 1)
  - Conflict in International Relations, 1986; 1986/155
    - African Institute for International Economic Policy, 1986 (Reel 4, Frame 137)
    - K-W, 1986 (Reel 4, Frame 351)
  - Health of Populations (HP)/Health Sciences (HS) - International Clinical Epidemiology Network (INCLEN), 1986; 1986/197
    - Zhang Yong-Yuan, 1986 (Reel 4, Frame 518)
  - United States, 1986; 1986/200
    - Africare (C-S), 1986 (Reel 4, Frame 522)
    - Ac-Al, 1986 (Reel 4, Frame 892)
    - American Association for Advancement of Science (Global Outreach), 1986 (Reel 5, Frame 1)
    - American Center for Students and Artists, 1986 (Reel 5, Frame 144)
    - American (A-E), 1986 (Reel 5, Frame 215)
    - American Public Health Association, 1986 (Reel 5, Frame 633)
    - American (P-V), 1986 (Reel 5, Frame 701)
    - An-Au, 1986 (Reel 6, Frame 1)
    - Ba-Bi, 1986 (Reel 6, Frame 566)
    - Briskey, Ernest J., 1986 (Reel 6, Frame 832)
    - Bl-By, 1986 (Reel 7, Frame 1)
    - Carnegie (C-M), 1986 (Reel 7, Frame 402)
    - Cal-Car, 1986 (Reel 7, Frame 832)
    - Cassava Workshop, 1986 (Reel 8, Frame 1)
    - Cas-Cav, 1986 (Reel 8, Frame 273)
    - Center for Foreign Language Pedagogy, 1986 (Reel 8, Frame 646)
    - Center (A-S), 1986 (Reel 8, Frame 833)
    - Ce-Ci, 1986 (Reel 9, Frame 1)
    - Cl, 1986 (Reel 9, Frame 279)
    - Coa-Com, 1986 (Reel 9, Frame 341)
    - Cornell University (B-S), 1986 (Reel 9, Frame 950)
    - Con-Cow, 1986 (Reel 10, Frame 1)
    - Critchfield, Richard, 1986 (Reel 10, Frame 478)
    - Cu, 1986 (Reel 10, Frame 742)
    - D, 1986 (Reel 10, Frame 752)
    - E, 1986 (Reel 11, Frame 1)
    - Ford Foundation (A-W), 1986 (Reel 11, Frame 268)
    - F, 1986 (Reel 11, Frame 496)
    - G, 1986 (Reel 12, Frame 1)
    - Harvard University (C-T), 1986 (Reel 12, Frame 360)
    - Ha, 1986 (Reel 12, Frame 888)
    - He-Ho, 1986 (Reel 13, Frame 1)
    - Individual Artists Funding (Conference), 1986 (Reel 13, Frame 625)
    - Insel, Barbara, 1986 (Reel 14, Frame 1)
    - International Health and Biomedicine ("Comprehending the Third World"), 1986 (Reel 14, Frame 111)
    - International (B-W), 1986 (Reel 14, Frame 262)
    - I, 1986 (Reel 15, Frame 1)
    - Johns Hopkins University (Clinical Epidemiology Resource and Training Center), 1986 (Reel 15, Frame 360)
    - J-K, 1986 (Reel 15, Frame 722)
    - L, 1986 (Reel 16, Frame 1)
    - Ma-Me, 1986 (Reel 16, Frame 174)
    - Mentor Group, 1986 (Reel 16, Frame 562)
    - Me-Mo, 1986 (Reel 16, Frame 685)
    - National (A-B), 1986 (Reel 17, Frame 1)
    - National Center for Urban Ethnic Affairs, 1986 (Reel 17, Frame 237)
    - National (C-E), 1986 (Reel 17, Frame 353)
    - National Hispanic University, 1986 (Reel 18, Frame 1)
    - National (F-M), 1986 (Reel 18, Frame 214)
    - National (N-U), 1986 (Reel 19, Frame 1)
    - National Public Radio - Performance Today Pilot: John Tyler, 1986; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15954)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Open for research. Digital access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
    - New York (A-Y), 1986 (Reel 19, Frame 418)
    - N, 1986 (Reel 20, Frame 1)
    - O, 1986 (Reel 20, Frame 416)
    - Parrish Art Museum, 1986 (Reel 20, Frame 665)
    - Phelps Stokes Fund, 1986 (Reel 20, Frame 668)
    - Phillips, S. Michael, 1986 (Reel 20, Frame 745)
    - Pa-Po, 1986 (Reel 21, Frame 1)
    - Pr-Pu, 1986 (Reel 21, Frame 499)
    - Resource Development Services, 1986 (Reel 21, Frame 845)
    - Rockefeller, 1986 (Reel 22, Frame 1)
    - Q-R, 1986 (Reel 22, Frame 51)
    - S-So, 1986 (Reel 22, Frame 266)
    - Se-Sm, 1986 (Reel 22, Frame 569)
    - So-Sp, 1986 (Reel 23, Frame 1)
    - St-Sz, 1986 (Reel 23, Frame 176)
    - T, 1986 (Reel 23, Frame 574)
    - University of California (B-W), 1986 (Reel 24, Frame 1)
    - University (A-H), 1986 (Reel 24, Frame 462)
    - University (I-W), 1986 (Reel 24, Frame 528)
    - U, 1986 (Reel 25, Frame 1)
    - WNET/13 (G-S), 1986 (Reel 25, Frame 538)
    - WQED (Projects Literacy, U.S.), 1986 (Reel 25, Frame 655)
    - Women's Action Alliance, Inc. (Conference), 1986 (Reel 26, Frame 1)
    - V-W, 1986 (Reel 26, Frame 191)
    - Yale University (C-R), 1986 (Reel 26, Frame 755)
    - Y-Z, 1986 (Reel 27, Frame 1)
    - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1986; 1986/200.E
      - C-D, 1986 (Reel 27, Frame 116)
      - Richardson, Edward J., 1986 (Reel 27, Frame 217)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, 1986; 1986/200.R
      - Guadalupe Cultural Arts Center (Cine Festival), 1986 (Reel 27, Frame 310)
  - Philippines, 1986; 1986/242
    - C-U, 1986 (Reel 27, Frame 410)
    - Philippines - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1986; 1986/242.D
      - Rice (Postdoctoral Fellows), 1986 (Reel 27, Frame 528)
  - Virgin Islands, 1986; 1986/257
    - College of the Virgin Islands, 1986 (Reel 27, Frame 545)
  - Fellowships for American Playwrights/Playwrights-in-Residence Program, 1986; 1986/272
    - T-W, 1986 (Reel 27, Frame 558)
  - Argentina, 1986; 1986/301
    - G-H, 1986 (Reel 27, Frame 574)
  - Brazil, 1986; 1986/305
    - B-U, 1986 (Reel 27, Frame 581)
  - Colombia, 1986; 1986/311
    - C-U, 1986 (Reel 27, Frame 617)
    - Colombia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1986; 1986/311.E
      - Nunez, Victor M., 1986 (Reel 27, Frame 784)
  - Costa Rica, 1986; 1986/313
    - Avirgan, Tony, 1986 (Reel 27, Frame 788)
  - Ecuador, 1986; 1986/317
    Ecuador
    - Union Nacional de Mujeres del Ecuador, 1986 (Reel 27, Frame 790)
  - Haiti, 1986; 1986/320
    - 320, 1986 (Reel 27, Frame 797)
    - Boucard, Adrien L., 1986 (Reel 27, Frame 800)
  - Honduras, 1986; 1986/321
    - Zamorano, 1986 (Reel 27, Frame 807)
  - Mexico, 1986; 1986/323
    - C-P, 1986 (Reel 28, Frame 1)
  - Peru, 1986; 1986/331
    - Universidad Peruana Cayetano Heredia, 1986 (Reel 28, Frame 140)
  - Venezuela, 1986; 1986/339
    - B-C, 1986 (Reel 28, Frame 143)
  - England, 1986; 1986/401
    - Charities Aid Foundation, 1986 (Reel 28, Frame 163)
    - Overseas Development Institute (Fellowship Program), 1986 (Reel 28, Frame 413)
    - Oxford University (Clinical Epidemiology Resource and Training Center), 1986 (Reel 28, Frame 504)
    - Plant Breeding Institute, England (Rice), 1986 (Reel 28, Frame 709)
    - Rural Investment Overseas, Ltd., 1986 (Reel 29, Frame 1)
    - University of Birmingham (Rice), 1986 (Reel 29, Frame 134)
    - A-U, 1986 (Reel 29, Frame 240)
  - Scotland, 1986; 1986/405
    - M-U, 1986 (Reel 30, Frame 1)
  - Australia, 1986; 1986/410
    - M-V, 1986 (Reel 30, Frame 62)
  - Guyana, 1986; 1986/423
    - Commonwealth Youth Programme (Caribbean Centre), 1986 (Reel 30, Frame 183)
  - Canada, 1986; 1986/427
    - C-P, 1986 (Reel 30, Frame 202)
  - Ceylon, 1986; 1986/462
    - Suriyakumaran, C., 1986 (Reel 30, Frame 849)
  - Hong Kong, 1986; 1986/463
    - Asian Student Association, 1986 (Reel 30, Frame 867)
  - India, 1986; 1986/464
    - C-T, 1986 (Reel 30, Frame 1035)
    - India - Medical Sciences, 1986; 1986/464.A
      - All Indian Institute (Rajalakshmi, M), 1986 (Reel 30, Frame 1069)
    - India - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1986; 1986/464.E
      - Ramakrishna Mission Lokasiksha Parishad, 1986 (Reel 30, Frame 1072)
  - Pakistan, 1986; 1986/465
    - A-H, 1986 (Reel 31, Frame 1)
  - Bengal/Bangladesh, 1986; 1986/466
    - B-R, 1986 (Reel 31, Frame 55)
  - Burma, 1986; 1986/468
    Myanmar
    - Than Swe, 1986 (Reel 31, Frame 80)
  - New Guinea and Papua, 1986; 1986/472
    - Alphers, Michael, 1986 (Reel 31, Frame 83)
  - Malaysia, 1986; 1986/473
    - Statistics, 1986 (Reel 31, Frame 86)
  - Nepal, 1986; 1986/474
    - B-P, 1986 (Reel 31, Frame 95)
  - Africa, 1986; 1986/475
    - African Chairs of Technology, 1986 (Reel 31, Frame 128)
  - Kenya, 1986; 1986/476
    - A-U, 1986 (Reel 31, Frame 169)
    - Kenya - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1986; 1986/476.E
      - Nyeko, J.H.P., 1986 (Reel 31, Frame 210)
  - East Africa Region, 1986; 1986/477
    - G-S, 1986 (Reel 31, Frame 219)
  - Rhodesia, 1986; 1986/483
    - National Gallery of Zimbabwe (Sibanda, Doreen), 1986 (Reel 31, Frame 234)
  - South Africa Region, 1986; 1986/487
    - National Museum and Art Gallery Botswana, 1986 (Reel 31, Frame 242)
  - Cape of Good Hope, 1986; 1986/489
    - I-U, 1986 (Reel 31, Frame 374)
  - Uganda, 1986; 1986/492
    - M-N, 1986 (Reel 31, Frame 418)
  - West Africa, 1986; 1986/495
    - West African Museums Project, 1986 (Reel 31, Frame 444)
  - Nigeria, 1986; 1986/497
    - O, 1986 (Reel 31, Frame 467)
  - France, 1986; 1986/500
    - G-P, 1986 (Reel 31, Frame 495)
  - Ivory Coast, 1986; 1986/527
    Ivory Coast
    - Agriculture, 1986 (Reel 32, Frame 1)
  - People's Republic of China, 1986; 1986/601
    - A-Z, 1986 (Reel 33, Frame 1)
  - Taiwan, 1986; 1986/605
    - Asian Vegetable Research and Development, 1986 (Reel 33, Frame 249)
  - Japan, 1986; 1986/609
    - H-N, 1986 (Reel 33, Frame 252)
    - Japan - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1986; 1986/609.D
      - Oono, Kiyoharu, 1986 (Reel 33, Frame 261)
  - Korea, 1986; 1986/613
    - Ro, Chung H., 1986 (Reel 33, Frame 264)
  - Thailand, 1986; 1986/617
    - A-Y, 1986 (Reel 33, Frame 273)
  - International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management (Genetic Improvement in Aquaculture), 1986; 1986/626
    - International Center For Living Aquatic Resources Management (Genetic Improvement in Aquaculture), 1986 (Reel 33, Frame 286)
  - Holland, 1986; 1986/650
    - A-V, 1986 (Reel 33, Frame 290)
  - Indonesia, 1986; 1986/652
    - C-M, 1986 (Reel 33, Frame 506)
  - Ethiopia, 1986; 1986/701
    - Addis Ababa University (Kidane, Asmerom), 1986 (Reel 33, Frame 534)
  - Belgium, 1986; 1986/707
    - D-E, 1986 (Reel 33, Frame 539)
  - Belgian Congo, 1986; 1986/709
    - Ngokwey, Ndolaml, 1986 (Reel 33, Frame 603)
  - Yugoslavia, 1986; 1986/710
    Yugoslavia
    - Sola, Tomislav, 1986 (Reel 33, Frame 606)
  - Germany, 1986; 1986/717
    - B-S, 1986 (Reel 33, Frame 613)
  - Tanganyika, 1986; 1986/723
    - K-U, 1986 (Reel 33, Frame 678)
  - Zambia, 1986; 1986/724
    - Mundende, D. Chongo, 1986 (Reel 33, Frame 689)
  - Greece, 1986; 1986/749
    - Antzoularou-Retsila, Eurydice, 1986 (Reel 33, Frame 692)
  - Italy, 1986; 1986/751
    - A-S, 1986 (Reel 33, Frame 741)
  - Poland, 1986; 1986/789
    - Poland - Nursing, 1986; 1986/789.C
      Nursing
      - University of Cracow, 1986 (Reel 33, Frame 866)
  - Sweden, 1986; 1986/800
    - Biejer Institute, 1986 (Reel 33, Frame 876)
  - Switzerland, 1986; 1986/803
    - C-P, 1986 (Reel 33, Frame 885)
  - Palestine/Israel, 1986; 1986/825
    - B-N, 1986 (Reel 34, Frame 1)
  - Lebanon, 1986; 1986/833
    - Beirut University College, 1986 (Reel 34, Frame 228)
  - Special Interests and Explorations (SIE) - Biotechnology Career Fellowships, 1986; 1986/860
    - H-Y, 1986 (Reel 34, Frame 245)
  - Members and Meetings, 1986; 1986/903
    - B-W, 1986 (Reel 34, Frame 388)
  - Humanities, 1986; 1986/911
    - Humanities - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1986; 1986/911.E
      - H-U, 1986 (Reel 34, Frame 421)
  - Great Neglected Diseases (GND)/Health Services (HS), 1986; 1986/928
    - David, John R., 1986 (Reel 34, Frame 769)
    - Great Neglected Diseases (GND)/Health Services (HS) - Career Development Fellowships in Geographic Medicine, 1986; 1986/928.E
      - Salzman, Andrew L., 1986 (Reel 34, Frame 871)
- General Correspondence, 1987; 0.37 Cubic Feet 28 microfilm reels (35mm); 28 Reels 28 microfilm reels (35mm)
  - International, 1987; 1987/100
    - Herdt, Robert W., 1987 (Reel 1, Frame 1)
    - Lyman, Richard W., 1987 (Reel 1, Frame 83)
    - Warren, Kenneth S., 1987 (Reel 1, Frame 311)
    - A-J, 1987 (Reel 1, Frame 315)
    - L-P, 1987 (Reel 1, Frame 590)
    - S-T, 1987 (Reel 1, Frame 675)
  - Requests for Information, 1987; 1987/102
    - Directories (D-N), 1987 (Reel 1, Frame 792)
  - International Organizations, 1987; 1987/103
    - International (B-C), 1987 (Reel 2, Frame 1)
    - International (F-U), 1987 (Reel 2, Frame 334)
    - United Nations (E-W), 1987 (Reel 2, Frame 485)
    - United Nations Development Fund for Women, 1987 (Reel 2, Frame 739)
    - United Nations Development Programme (B-R), 1987 (Reel 2, Frame 769)
    - United Nations Educational Scientific and Cultural Organization (International Fund for the Promotion of Culture), 1987 (Reel 3, Frame 1)
    - United Nations Fund for Population Activities (Sadik, Nafis), 1987 (Reel 3, Frame 4)
    - United Nations University (Soedjatmoko), 1987 (Reel 3, Frame 6)
    - B-N, 1987 (Reel 3, Frame 16)
    - S-T, 1987 (Reel 3, Frame 371)
    - W, 1987 (Reel 3, Frame 629)
  - IITA (International Institute of Tropical Agriculture - Nigeria), 1987; 1987/115
    - 115, 1987 (Reel 4, Frame 1)
  - International Center for Agricultural Research in the Dry Areas, 1987; 1987/118
    - International Center for Agricultural Research in the Dry Areas, 1987 (Reel 4, Frame 11)
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 1987; 1987/120
    - Naquin, Susan, 1987 (Reel 4, Frame 14)
    - Odyssey Institute Corp. (Densen-Gerber, Judianne), 1987 (Reel 4, Frame 62)
    - O'Toole, Lawrence Michael, 1987 (Reel 4, Frame 148)
    - Trueba, Henry T., 1987 (Reel 4, Frame 235)
    - C-W, 1987 (Reel 4, Frame 291)
  - Greater Voice for Africa in the United States (Africa Policy Watch Project), 1987; 1987/121
    - A-N, 1987 (Reel 4, Frame 389)
  - Equal Opportunity - Basic Rights/Policy Research, 1987/175
    - Equal Opportunity - Basic Rights/Policy Research - Fellowships, 1987; 1987/175.E
      - C-G, 1987 (Reel 4, Frame 637)
  - United States, 1987; 1987/200
    - Ac-Al, 1987 (Reel 4, Frame 720)
    - American (A-E), 1987 (Reel 5, Frame 1)
    - American (F-S), 1987 (Reel 5, Frame 283)
    - Am-Ay, 1987 (Reel 5, Frame 775)
    - Baltimore Process, Inc. (Underclass Issues), 1987 (Reel 6, Frame 1)
    - B, 1987 (Reel 6, Frame 54)
    - Case Western Reserve University (M-S), 1987 (Reel 6, Frame 615)
    - Ca, 1987 (Reel 7, Frame 1)
    - Center (A-S), 1987 (Reel 7, Frame 488)
    - Ce-Ci, 1987 (Reel 7, Frame 715)
    - Colorado State University (K-T), 1987 (Reel 8, Frame 1)
    - Columbia University (A-R), 1987 (Reel 8, Frame 85)
    - Cornell University (A-S), 1987 (Reel 8, Frame 181)
    - Council (C-U), 1987 (Reel 8, Frame 222)
    - Cl-Co, 1987 (Reel 8, Frame 324)
    - Cr-Cu, 1987 (Reel 8, Frame 616)
    - Duke University (C-T), 1987 (Reel 8, Frame 723)
    - D, 1987 (Reel 9, Frame 1)
    - E, 1987 (Reel 9, Frame 195)
    - Ford Foundation (B-W), 1987 (Reel 9, Frame 461)
    - F, 1987 (Reel 9, Frame 575)
    - G, 1987 (Reel 10, Frame 1)
    - Harvard University (C-S), 1987 (Reel 10, Frame 181)
    - Ha-He, 1987 (Reel 10, Frame 272)
    - Hi-Hu, 1987 (Reel 10, Frame 458)
    - International (D-W), 1987 (Reel 10, Frame 758)
    - I, 1987 (Reel 11, Frame 1)
    - J, 1987 (Reel 11, Frame 649)
    - K, 1987 (Reel 12, Frame 1)
    - L, 1987 (Reel 12, Frame 185)
    - Ma-Me, 1987 (Reel 12, Frame 499)
    - Michigan State University (A-L), 1987 (Reel 12, Frame 683)
    - Mt. Holyoke College - Worldwide Education for Women, 1987 (Reel 12, Frame 822)
    - Mi-Mu, 1987 (Reel 13, Frame 1)
    - National Academy of Sciences (E-H), 1987 (Reel 13, Frame 225)
    - National (A-C), 1987 (Reel 13, Frame 352)
    - National (D-W), 1987 (Reel 13, Frame 669)
    - New (A-W), 1987 (Reel 14, Frame 1)
    - New York City (C-T), 1987 (Reel 14, Frame 256)
    - New York (C-U), 1987 (Reel 14, Frame 485)
    - N, 1987 (Reel 14, Frame 616)
    - O, 1987 (Reel 14, Frame 700)
    - P, 1987 (Reel 15, Frame 1)
    - Population Reports International, 1987 (Reel 15, Frame 336)
    - Rockefeller, 1987 (Reel 15, Frame 345)
    - R, 1987 (Reel 15, Frame 376)
    - Sa-Sk, 1987 (Reel 15, Frame 602)
    - Smithsonian Institution (E-U), 1987 (Reel 15, Frame 900)
    - Southern (C-R), 1987 (Reel 16, Frame 1)
    - Stanford University (F-W), 1987 (Reel 16, Frame 127)
    - Sm-Sy, 1987 (Reel 16, Frame 191)
    - Technologies Related to Health in Developing Countries (Conference), 1987 (Reel 16, Frame 559)
    - T, 1987 (Reel 16, Frame 596)
    - University (A-H), 1987 (Reel 16, Frame 843)
    - University (I-W), 1987 (Reel 17, Frame 1)
    - U, 1987 (Reel 17, Frame 310)
    - V-Wh, 1987 (Reel 17, Frame 561)
    - Wi-Wo, 1987 (Reel 18, Frame 1)
    - Y, 1987 (Reel 18, Frame 237)
    - United States - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1987; 1987/200.D
      - University of Idaho (Agriculture), 1987 (Reel 18, Frame 553)
    - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1987; 1987/200.E
      - Castro, Alfonso Peter, 1987 (Reel 18, Frame 657)
      - Driscoll, Paul J., 1987 (Reel 18, Frame 663)
      - M-O, 1987 (Reel 18, Frame 746)
  - Philippines, 1987; 1987/242
    - C-W, 1987 (Reel 18, Frame 854)
    - Philippines - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1987; 1987/242.D
      - International Rice Research Institute (Juliano, Bienvenido O.), 1987 (Reel 18, Frame 946)
  - Puerto Rico, 1987; 1987/243
    - Inter-American University of Puerto Rico, 1987 (Reel 18, Frame 983)
  - Fellowships for American Playwrights/Playwrights-in-Residence Program, 1987; 1987/272
    - L-P, 1987 (Reel 18, Frame 988)
  - South America, also Latin America and Central America, 1987; 1987/300
    - Inter-American Institute for Cooperation on Agriculture, 1987 (Reel 19, Frame 1)
  - Argentina, 1987; 1987/301
    - N-T, 1987 (Reel 19, Frame 35)
  - Brazil, 1987; 1987/305
    - G-S, 1987 (Reel 19, Frame 96)
  - Chile, 1987; 1987/309
    - C-F, 1987 (Reel 19, Frame 127)
  - Colombia, 1987; 1987/311
    - Instituto de Integracion Cultural Recinto de Quirama, 1987 (Reel 19, Frame 176)
  - Costa Rica, 1987; 1987/313
    - University of Costa Rica, 1987 (Reel 19, Frame 193)
  - Honduras, 1987; 1987/321
    - Zamorano, 1987 (Reel 19, Frame 227)
  - Mexico, 1987; 1987/323
    - Institute of Health and Tropical Diseases, 1987 (Reel 19, Frame 371)
    - A-L, 1987 (Reel 19, Frame 437)
  - Republic of Panama, 1987; 1987/327
    - Valdes Escoffery, Eduardo, 1987 (Reel 19, Frame 519)
  - Peru, 1987; 1987/331
    - Nutrition Research Institute, Peru (Graham, George G.), 1987 (Reel 19, Frame 523)
  - England, 1987; 1987/401
    - America-European Community Association (Arts Conference), 1987 (Reel 19, Frame 560)
    - CAB International, 1987 (Reel 19, Frame 716)